[
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Tujuh",
    "options": [
      "fünf",
      "sieben",
      "vier",
      "acht"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sieben"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Putih",
    "options": [
      "blau",
      "schwarz",
      "weiß",
      "rot"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "weiß"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Selasa",
    "options": [
      "Montag",
      "Dienstag",
      "Donnerstag",
      "Freitag"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Dienstag"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "April",
    "options": [
      "April",
      "Mai",
      "Juni",
      "Juli"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "April"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Anak laki-laki",
    "options": [
      "Mädchen",
      "Junge",
      "Frau",
      "Mann"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Junge"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Roti",
    "options": [
      "Fleisch",
      "Brot",
      "Kaffee",
      "Saft"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Brot"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Membaca",
    "options": [
      "lesen",
      "schreiben",
      "singen",
      "tanzen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "lesen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Komputer",
    "options": [
      "Fernseher",
      "Computer",
      "Bild",
      "Schlüssel"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Computer"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Harimau",
    "options": [
      "Löwe",
      "Tiger",
      "Bär",
      "Elefant"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Tiger"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Toko",
    "options": [
      "Café",
      "Museum",
      "Laden",
      "Apotheke"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Laden"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Halo",
    "options": [
      "Guten Tag",
      "Hallo",
      "Tschüss",
      "Ja"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Hallo"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Apa",
    "options": [
      "Wer",
      "Was",
      "Wo",
      "Warum"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Was"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Mudah",
    "options": [
      "schwer",
      "einfach",
      "bunt",
      "billig"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "einfach"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Kemarin",
    "options": [
      "heute",
      "morgen",
      "gestern",
      "jetzt"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gestern"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Panjang",
    "options": [
      "kurz",
      "lang",
      "laut",
      "leicht"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "lang"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Sering",
    "options": [
      "oft",
      "selten",
      "nie",
      "schnell"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "oft"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Kuat",
    "options": [
      "traurig",
      "stark",
      "schwach",
      "langsam"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "stark"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Hangat",
    "options": [
      "kalt",
      "warm",
      "schnell",
      "neu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "warm"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Bersama",
    "options": [
      "zusammen",
      "allein",
      "oben",
      "unten"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "zusammen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "Rumah sakit",
    "options": [
      "Apotheke",
      "Kino",
      "Krankenhaus",
      "Supermarkt"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Krankenhaus"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Sembilan",
    "options": [
      "sieben",
      "acht",
      "neun",
      "zehn"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "neun"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Coklat",
    "options": [
      "orange",
      "braun",
      "weiß",
      "grau"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "braun"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Jumat",
    "options": [
      "Montag",
      "Freitag",
      "Dienstag",
      "Sonntag"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Freitag"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Juni",
    "options": [
      "Mai",
      "Juli",
      "Juni",
      "August"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Juni"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Kakek",
    "options": [
      "Onkel",
      "Großvater",
      "Vater",
      "Bruder"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Großvater"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Telur",
    "options": [
      "Käse",
      "Fleisch",
      "Ei",
      "Brot"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Ei"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Mengatakan",
    "options": [
      "sagen",
      "machen",
      "hören",
      "lesen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sagen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Jendela",
    "options": [
      "Fernseher",
      "Tür",
      "Fenster",
      "Schlüssel"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Fenster"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Singa",
    "options": [
      "Bär",
      "Löwe",
      "Tiger",
      "Elefant"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Löwe"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Restoran",
    "options": [
      "Supermarkt",
      "Apotheke",
      "Restaurant",
      "Café"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Restaurant"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Selamat malam",
    "options": [
      "Guten Tag",
      "Hallo",
      "Gute Nacht",
      "Tschüss"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Gute Nacht"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Mengapa",
    "options": [
      "Wo",
      "Wann",
      "Warum",
      "Was"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Warum"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Murah",
    "options": [
      "billig",
      "teuer",
      "bunt",
      "schwer"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "billig"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Sebentar lagi",
    "options": [
      "gestern",
      "morgen",
      "bald",
      "heute"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "bald"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Kecil",
    "options": [
      "groß",
      "klein",
      "lang",
      "kurz"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "klein"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Jarang",
    "options": [
      "oft",
      "selten",
      "nie",
      "schnell"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "selten"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Sedih",
    "options": [
      "glücklich",
      "traurig",
      "schön",
      "stark"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "traurig"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Cukup",
    "options": [
      "laut",
      "genug",
      "langsam",
      "schnell"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "genug"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Bersama",
    "options": [
      "allein",
      "zusammen",
      "unten",
      "oben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "zusammen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "Supermarket",
    "options": [
      "Kino",
      "Bank",
      "Supermarkt",
      "Apotheke"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Supermarkt"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Tiga belas",
    "options": [
      "zwölf",
      "vierzehn",
      "dreizehn",
      "fünfzehn"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "dreizehn"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Oranye",
    "options": [
      "weiß",
      "grau",
      "orange",
      "braun"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "orange"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "April",
    "options": [
      "Mai",
      "Juni",
      "März",
      "April"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "April"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Juli",
    "options": [
      "Mai",
      "Juni",
      "Juli",
      "August"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Juli"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Keponakan",
    "options": [
      "Nichte",
      "Neffe",
      "Tante",
      "Bruder"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Neffe"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Pisang",
    "options": [
      "Apfel",
      "Banane",
      "Traube",
      "Orange"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Banane"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Membaca",
    "options": [
      "schreiben",
      "hören",
      "lesen",
      "sagen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "lesen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Kunci",
    "options": [
      "Tasche",
      "Uhr",
      "Schlüssel",
      "Bild"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Schlüssel"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Harimau",
    "options": [
      "Löwe",
      "Elefant",
      "Tiger",
      "Kamel"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Tiger"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Museum",
    "options": [
      "Bank",
      "Apotheke",
      "Restaurant",
      "Museum"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Museum"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Sampai jumpa lagi",
    "options": [
      "Hallo",
      "Guten Tag",
      "Auf Wiedersehen",
      "Tschüss"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Auf Wiedersehen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Dimana",
    "options": [
      "Warum",
      "Wo",
      "Wann",
      "Was"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Wo"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Segar",
    "options": [
      "warm",
      "frisch",
      "laut",
      "schnell"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "frisch"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Indah",
    "options": [
      "hässlich",
      "schön",
      "traurig",
      "stark"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "schön"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Panjang",
    "options": [
      "lang",
      "kurz",
      "langsam",
      "bunt"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "lang"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Tidak ramah",
    "options": [
      "freundlich",
      "nett",
      "unfreundlich",
      "stark"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "unfreundlich"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Buruk",
    "options": [
      "schlecht",
      "schön",
      "stark",
      "traurig"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "schlecht"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Hangat",
    "options": [
      "kalt",
      "warm",
      "langsam",
      "groß"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "warm"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Bersama",
    "options": [
      "allein",
      "zusammen",
      "unten",
      "oben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "zusammen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "Gereja",
    "options": [
      "Bank",
      "Kirche",
      "Supermarkt",
      "Museum"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Kirche"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Dua belas",
    "options": [
      "dreizehn",
      "zwölf",
      "elf",
      "vierzehn"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "zwölf"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Merah muda",
    "options": [
      "grau",
      "rosa",
      "weiß",
      "braun"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "rosa"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "September",
    "options": [
      "Oktober",
      "August",
      "September",
      "Juli"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "September"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "November",
    "options": [
      "Dezember",
      "November",
      "Oktober",
      "Januar"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "November"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Sepupu laki-laki",
    "options": [
      "Cousine",
      "Neffe",
      "Cousin",
      "Bruder"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Jus",
    "options": [
      "Wasser",
      "Saft",
      "Tee",
      "Milch"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Saft"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Menulis",
    "options": [
      "hören",
      "lesen",
      "schreiben",
      "sagen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "schreiben"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Televisi",
    "options": [
      "Fenster",
      "Kühlschrank",
      "Fernseher",
      "Bild"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Fernseher"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Beruang",
    "options": [
      "Löwe",
      "Elefant",
      "Bär",
      "Kamel"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Bär"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Kafe",
    "options": [
      "Restaurant",
      "Supermarkt",
      "Kino",
      "Café"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Café"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Selamat datang",
    "options": [
      "Tschüss",
      "Willkommen",
      "Hallo",
      "Auf Wiedersehen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Willkommen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Bagaimana",
    "options": [
      "Warum",
      "Wie",
      "Wann",
      "Wo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Wie"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Awal",
    "options": [
      "spät",
      "früh",
      "schnell",
      "bunt"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "früh"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Hari ini",
    "options": [
      "gestern",
      "heute",
      "morgen",
      "bald"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "heute"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Diam-diam",
    "options": [
      "laut",
      "bunt",
      "ruhig",
      "frisch"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ruhig"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Jarang",
    "options": [
      "oft",
      "schnell",
      "selten",
      "nie"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "selten"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Lemah",
    "options": [
      "stark",
      "langsam",
      "schwach",
      "traurig"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "schwach"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Cukup",
    "options": [
      "genug",
      "schlecht",
      "leicht",
      "stark"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "genug"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Jalan",
    "options": [
      "Brücke",
      "Straße",
      "Kirche",
      "Laden"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Straße"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "Balaikota",
    "options": [
      "Bank",
      "Krankenhaus",
      "Rathaus",
      "Kino"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Rathaus"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Empat puluh",
    "options": [
      "fünfzig",
      "vierzig",
      "dreißig",
      "zwanzig"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "vierzig"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Abu-abu",
    "options": [
      "grau",
      "weiß",
      "braun",
      "schwarz"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "grau"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Agustus",
    "options": [
      "Juli",
      "September",
      "August",
      "Oktober"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "August"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Desember",
    "options": [
      "Dezember",
      "November",
      "Januar",
      "Oktober"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Dezember"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Sepupu perempuan",
    "options": [
      "Cousin",
      "Tante",
      "Cousine",
      "Schwester"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Cousine"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Makanan ringan",
    "options": [
      "Schokolade",
      "Snacks",
      "Käse",
      "Brot"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Snacks"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Mendengar",
    "options": [
      "schreiben",
      "hören",
      "sagen",
      "lesen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "hören"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Microwave",
    "options": [
      "Kühlschrank",
      "Fernseher",
      "Mikrowelle",
      "Schlüssel"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Mikrowelle"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Katak",
    "options": [
      "Löwe",
      "Bär",
      "Frosch",
      "Elefant"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Frosch"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Kantor polisi",
    "options": [
      "Postamt",
      "Polizeistation",
      "Krankenhaus",
      "Bank"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Polizeistation"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Ya",
    "options": [
      "Nein",
      "Ja",
      "Vielleicht",
      "Willkommen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Ja"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Apa",
    "options": [
      "Wer",
      "Was",
      "Wann",
      "Wo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Was"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Bagus",
    "options": [
      "schlecht",
      "schön",
      "stark",
      "traurig"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "schön"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Sering",
    "options": [
      "oft",
      "selten",
      "schnell",
      "nie"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "oft"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Lantang, nyaring",
    "options": [
      "leise",
      "laut",
      "bunt",
      "langsam"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "laut"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Besok",
    "options": [
      "gestern",
      "morgen",
      "heute",
      "bald"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "morgen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Tidak ramah",
    "options": [
      "freundlich",
      "nett",
      "unfreundlich",
      "stark"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "unfreundlich"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Di atas",
    "options": [
      "oben",
      "unten",
      "allein",
      "zusammen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "oben"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Kolam renang",
    "options": [
      "Schwimmbad",
      "Supermarkt",
      "Kino",
      "Apotheke"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Schwimmbad"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A1",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "Jembatan",
    "options": [
      "Kirche",
      "Straße",
      "Brücke",
      "Bank"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Brücke"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "selain itu",
    "options": [
      "spannend",
      "indirekt",
      "außerdem",
      "müssen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "außerdem"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "nyaman",
    "options": [
      "benutzen",
      "bequem",
      "beliebt",
      "sterben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "bequem"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "lebar",
    "options": [
      "unbeliebt",
      "interessiert",
      "breit",
      "unbequem"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "breit"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "langsung",
    "options": [
      "mutig",
      "können",
      "liegen",
      "direkt"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "direkt"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "di luar",
    "options": [
      "einsteigen",
      "reservieren",
      "obwohl",
      "draußen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "draußen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "di dalam",
    "options": [
      "unpünktlich",
      "pünktlich",
      "aussteigen",
      "drinnen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "drinnen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "tipis",
    "options": [
      "verlieren",
      "dünn",
      "unbequem",
      "vielleicht"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "dünn"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "sempit",
    "options": [
      "passen",
      "eng",
      "obwohl",
      "legen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "eng"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "serius",
    "options": [
      "breit",
      "ernst",
      "modern",
      "sterben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ernst"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 1",
    "question": "dengan senang hati",
    "options": [
      "kostenpflichtig",
      "für",
      "jedoch",
      "gern"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gern"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "keras",
    "options": [
      "pünktlich",
      "hart",
      "dünn",
      "arm"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "hart"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "tidak langsung",
    "options": [
      "dünn",
      "bleiben",
      "modern",
      "indirekt"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "indirekt"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "namun",
    "options": [
      "jedoch",
      "modern",
      "beliebt",
      "ernst"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "jedoch"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "jarang, hampir tidak",
    "options": [
      "kaum",
      "sauer",
      "sterben",
      "arm"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kaum"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "kreatif",
    "options": [
      "sauer",
      "bleiben",
      "kreativ",
      "unbequem"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kreativ"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "membosankan",
    "options": [
      "langweilig",
      "ausmachen",
      "arm",
      "bleiben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "langweilig"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "logis",
    "options": [
      "interessiert",
      "unbequem",
      "verlassen",
      "logisch"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "logisch"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "modern",
    "options": [
      "modern",
      "beliebt",
      "liefern",
      "erlauben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "modern"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "berani",
    "options": [
      "wenig",
      "mutig",
      "reparieren",
      "setzen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mutig"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 2",
    "question": "tepat waktu",
    "options": [
      "pünktlich",
      "vergessen",
      "interessiert",
      "bleiben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pünktlich"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "asam",
    "options": [
      "sauer",
      "setzen",
      "unpünktlich",
      "langweilig"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sauer"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "menarik",
    "options": [
      "hängen",
      "spannend",
      "ernst",
      "verlassen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "spannend"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "disukai",
    "options": [
      "ausgeben",
      "bequem",
      "beliebt",
      "sterben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "beliebt"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "meskipun",
    "options": [
      "obwohl",
      "können",
      "sollen",
      "jedoch"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "obwohl"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "tidak nyaman",
    "options": [
      "wenig",
      "unbequem",
      "beliebt",
      "langweilig"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "unbequem"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "kasar",
    "options": [
      "kaum",
      "rau",
      "erklären",
      "sauer"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "rau"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "tidak tepat waktu",
    "options": [
      "bleiben",
      "kostenpflichtig",
      "sollen",
      "unpünktlich"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "unpünktlich"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "tidak disukai",
    "options": [
      "arm",
      "können",
      "setzen",
      "unbeliebt"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "unbeliebt"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "sebelumnya",
    "options": [
      "kostenpflichtig",
      "beliebt",
      "ausziehen",
      "vorher"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "vorher"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 3",
    "question": "mungkin",
    "options": [
      "hängen",
      "korrigieren",
      "kaum",
      "vielleicht"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "vielleicht"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "kurang",
    "options": [
      "spannend",
      "arm",
      "wenig",
      "langweilig"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wenig"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "penting",
    "options": [
      "wichtig",
      "setzen",
      "ausmachen",
      "mögen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wichtig"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "tertarik",
    "options": [
      "drinnen",
      "abholen",
      "interessiert",
      "beliebt"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "interessiert"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "menjemput",
    "options": [
      "unbeliebt",
      "einsteigen",
      "hängen",
      "abholen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "abholen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "memulai",
    "options": [
      "benutzen",
      "anfangen",
      "spannend",
      "sollen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "anfangen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "mengenakan pakaian",
    "options": [
      "beliebt",
      "anziehen",
      "gern haben",
      "bequem"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "anziehen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "mengeluarkan uang",
    "options": [
      "ausgeben",
      "eng",
      "bequem",
      "gern haben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ausgeben"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "menonaktifkan",
    "options": [
      "langweilig",
      "jedoch",
      "drinnen",
      "ausmachen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ausmachen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "terlihat/muncul",
    "options": [
      "kostenpflichtig",
      "kaum",
      "aussehen",
      "können"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aussehen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 4",
    "question": "turun/keluar",
    "options": [
      "hängen",
      "unbequem",
      "kostenpflichtig",
      "aussteigen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aussteigen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "melepas pakaian",
    "options": [
      "sauer",
      "ausziehen",
      "interessiert",
      "bequem"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ausziehen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "memperhatikan",
    "options": [
      "abholen",
      "verlieren",
      "für",
      "aufpassen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "aufpassen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "menggunakan",
    "options": [
      "benutzen",
      "bleiben",
      "dünn",
      "aussehen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "benutzen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "menginap/tinggal",
    "options": [
      "obwohl",
      "unbequem",
      "vorher",
      "bleiben"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "bleiben"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "naik/masuk",
    "options": [
      "einsteigen",
      "eng",
      "langweilig",
      "kreativ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "einsteigen"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "menjelaskan",
    "options": [
      "obwohl",
      "aufpassen",
      "verlassen",
      "erklären"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "erklären"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "mengizinkan",
    "options": [
      "kaum",
      "pünktlich",
      "erlauben",
      "draußen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "erlauben"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "suka, menyenangkan",
    "options": [
      "pünktlich",
      "gern haben",
      "wollen",
      "anziehen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gern haben"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "untuk",
    "options": [
      "gern",
      "für",
      "sauer",
      "vorher"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "für"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "difficulty": "A2",
    "levelmark": "Level 5",
    "question": "mengucapkan selamat",
    "options": [
      "gratulieren",
      "anfangen",
      "ausgeben",
      "obwohl"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gratulieren"
  }
]